拜托！
Oh,come on!
你们也要过感恩节 不要老看足球，来帮帮忙
It's your Thanksgiving too. Instead of watching football,you could help.
我们知道啊
We know.
你要把棉花糖排成同心圆
You wanna put the marshmallows in concentric circles.
不，是你要把棉花糖 排成同心圆
No,you want to put them in concentric circles.
我要的是这样
I want to do this.
年年如此
Every year.
本集播出：“足球”
The One With the Football
十码、五码 触地得分，太棒了
To the 10,to the 5. Touchdown,Giants!
我倒想试试看看足球
You know,for once,I am gonna try to watch one of these things.
中场休息
Halftime.
谁想出去玩玩球？ 来个3对3？
Who wants to throw the ball around? Get a little 3-on-3 going?
一定很好玩 我可以参加吗？
-That would be fun! -Can I play too?
我从来没玩过足球
I've never played football,ever.
太好了，你可以防守钱德
Great! You can cover Chandler.
我不想玩球
I don't really want to play.
你跟珍妮丝分手之后 就一直提不起劲
You never do anything since you and Janice broke up.
才不是这样
Not true.
我想整天穿着浴袍吃花生
I wanted to wear my bathrobe and eat peanut clusters all day.
我还想在早上喝酒 别说我没有目标
And start drinking in the morning. Don't say I don't have goals!
你得把她忘了，好吗？
You have to start getting over her,all right?
如果你来玩球，呼吸新鲜空气 也许就会忘记珍妮丝
If you play,maybe it'll take your mind off Janice.
否则大家都会生你的气 因为这样两队人数就不平均了
If you don't,everyone will be mad at you because the teams won't be even.
好，我参加
All right,I'll play.
但是我不喜欢你
But l don't like you.
来吧，罗斯？
Let's do it! Ross?
什么？ 想玩足球吗？
-What? -Wanna play football?
莫妮卡跟我都不能玩足球
Monica and I aren't supposed to play football.
谁说的？你妈？
Says who? Your mom?
“你是什么意思？”她问她的男朋友
''What do you mean?''she asks her boyfriend...
惊恐地听着答案
...really scared to hear the answer.
以前每年圣诞节 我们都玩触身美式足球
Every Thanksgiving,we used to have a touch football game...
叫做盖勒杯
...called The Geller Bowl.
不…你的口气要很骄傲才对
No,no,no. You say that proudly!
反正罗斯跟我每次都当队长
Anyway,Ross and l were always captains.
竞争越来越激烈 有一年，第六届盖勒杯
It got kind of competitive,and one year,Geller Bowl Vl...
我不小心打断罗斯的鼻子
... I accidentally broke Ross' nose.
很明显不是偶然的
It was so not an accident.
她看到我就快抱住她 就用她的…
She saw I was about to tag her,so she threw...
大胖手肘撞我的脸
... her big fat grandma-arm elbow in my face...
然后拼命往前跑
...and just kept running.
因此赢得致胜的一分
To score the winning touchdown,by the way.
你没有赢，那次得分不算
You did not win the game. The touchdown didn't count...
因为你公然犯规 野蛮地打断我的鼻子
... because of the spectacularly illegal,and savage,nose-breaking.
我赢了
I won the game.
是吗？ 那你怎么没得到盖勒奖杯？
Yeah? Then how come you didn't get the Geller Cup?
有盖勒奖杯？
There was a Geller Cup?
对，这是赢球的奖品
Yes,the trophy you got if you won the game.
但爸爸说我们谁都没赢 他受够了我们打来打去
But Dad said nobody won,and he was sick of our fighting.
所以他把奖品…
So he took the trophy...
丢进湖里
...threw it in the lake.
这个诅咒解除了没有？
And was the curse lifted?
反正…
Anyway...
妈妈说我们不能再玩足球了
... Mom said we weren't allowed to play football again.
你知道吗？ 我觉得我们应该一起去玩球
You know what? I think we should play a game.
我是说，都已经过了12年了
I mean,come on. It's been 12 years.
跟你私下说句话好吗？
Can I see you for a second?
懦夫
Wuss!
好，我们参加
All right,we're gonna play.
等等，我们怎么过去？ 我妈不准我过马路
Wait. How we gonna get there? My mom won't let me cross the street.
来
Here you go.
把球丢过来 等等
-Let's bring it in. -Wait.
亲爱的，把球传给我
Honey,throw it to me!
来
Here you go.
你差点打中我的脸
That almost hit me in the face!
我们要选队长（与“船长”同字）
We have to pick captains.
还有“坦尼尔们”（肥皂剧《船长与坦尼尔》的女主角）
And then "Tennille."
我们怎么决定队长？
So how do we decide that?
装兔宝宝好不好？ 什么？
-Why don't we just bunny up? -What?
兔子 兔子
-Bunny! -Bunny!
看来队长就是罗斯跟我了
Looks like Ross and I are captains.
那些在高中跟你们混的人，肯定都上天堂了
There must be a place in heaven for people who hung out with you in high school.
我先装兔子 所以我先挑，乔伊
I bunnied first,so I get to pick first. Joey.
谢谢 莫妮卡
-Thank you. -Monica!
我是你最好的朋友
I'm your best friend.
甜心，别担心，会有人选你的 钱德
Sweetie,don't worry,you'll get picked.Chandler
-罗斯！-菲比
-Ross！-Phoebe
甜心，现在我选你了
Sweetie,now I pick you.
你才没选我 你只能选我了
You don't pick me. You're stuck with me!
好，这样吧
Okay. So let's see.
比赛场地是 从垃圾桶到路灯，好吗？
Let's play from the trash can to the light post,right?
两手发球，开始吧
Two-hand touch. We'll kick off.
大家听好了，28分钟后…
People,listen. I've got 28 minutes...
我就给你们好看
... before I have to baste again.
哇，就跟职业球队一样
Wow,just like in the pros.
好，临场会议
Okay,huddle up!
临场会议 等等我…
-Huddle up over here! -Wait for me! Wait for me!
太棒了！这是我的第一次
Oh,cool! My first huddle.
老实说 你们觉得钱德怎么样？
So what do you guys really think of Chandler?
你知道自己在做什么吧？
You know what you're doing,right?
乔伊接球，我们阻挡
Joey will catch it. We'll block.
什么叫“阻挡”？
What's "block"?
我还以为你知道自己在做什么 我以为你是指人生的方向
-I thought you knew what you were doing. -I thought you meant in life!
结束
Break!
球是珍妮丝…
The ball is Janice. The ball is Janice.
该死…
Son of a!
拜托 对不起…
-Come on! -I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
这样吧，我们用丢的好了
You know what? We're just gonna throw it.
我来接
I got it!
快…
Go,go,go!
得分，7比0
Score! Seven to nothing!
亲爱的，我很确信这件事
Honey,just so that l'm clear on this.
刚才临场会议的时候你说只要乔伊拿到球 你就去阻止他
You said in the huddle that if Joey caught the ball, you'd be the one to stop him.
而你并没有，这是足球策略吗？
Now, you didn't.So is that like a football strategy?
是的，这是我摔倒战术的一部分
Yeah, it was part of my plan to fall instantly behind. So....
我们来
Come on,let's go.
输家滚蛋
Losers walk.
是吗？输家只会说
Yeah? Losers talk.
其实输家是押韵的
Actually,losers rhyme.
43…
Forty-three...
74…
...seventy-four....
拉开进攻阵式好吗？ 好
You wanna go shotgun?
一个密西西比、两个密西西比（美国人数秒的方法） 这里…
-One Mississippi,two Mississippi.... -Over here! Over here!
我差点就接到了！
I almost caught it!
太好了，现在的比分是7比 差一点7
Great. Now the score's seven to almost seven.
这场比赛，我要你往前场跑 再用假动作往右边跑，好吗？
On this play,I want you to do a down-and-out to the right,okay?
开始 等等，那我要干嘛？
-Break! -Wait. What am I gonna do?
你？
You?
你跑远一点
You go long.
多远？
How long?
到你几乎看不见我们为止
Until we start to look very small.
开始
Break!
一个密西西比、两个密西西比…
One Mississippi
换防守位置…
Switch! Switch! Switch!
谢谢你挡住了我们的球
Thanks for stopping our ball.
你们在玩美式足球？
You are playing American football?
哇！你好像来自其他国家
Wow! You're,like,from a whole other country!
我是荷兰人
I'm Dutch.
嗨，我是乔伊（乔伊以为“荷兰人”是人名）
Hi,I'm Joey.
我是玛嘉
I am Margha.
对不起，荷兰人 最后一个字我没听懂
Sorry,Dutch,I didn't get that last little bit.
乔伊，你玩球还是… 嗨，我是钱德
You wanna play football or Hi,I'm Chandler.
你好，钱德
Hello,Chandler.
她叫做荷兰人，又叫做玛亨
Her name is Dutch and also "Margham."
你们，调情的男孩，我们在比赛
Yo, flirty boys.We're in the middle of a game.
来吧，开始了 第二次十码进攻
Come on,guys! Let's go! Second down!
喂，是第三次十码进攻了 才不是，这是第二次而已
-Hello? It's third down. -No,it's not. It's second.
哇！
Wow.
哇什么？
"Wow" what?
我真没想到你现在还来这一套
How it just amazes me that you're still pulling stuff like this.
哪一套？这是第二次进攻 好，是第二次进攻
-Pulling what? It's second down. -Okay,it's second down.
你要来几个第二次进攻都可以
Take all the second downs you need.
我听到了 我就是说给你听的
-I heard that. -Well,I said it loud.
我可以留下来看吗？
It is okay if I stay and watch?
我现在还不能回家
l can't go home just yet.
我的室友是个很差劲的美国商人
My roommate is forshlocking a big American businessman.
你只管坐着看 对啊，留下来吧
-Just sit right there. -Yeah,why don't you stick around?
很顺利 我想也是
-That went well. -I think so.
我想跟她要电话号码
I was thinking about asking her for her number.
谢了，老兄 但我自己开口比较有说服力
Thanks,man,but it makes a stronger statement if I ask for it myself.
我是替我自己要的 好帮我忘了珍妮丝
I was thinking about for me,as part of that getting-over-Janice thing.
对啊
Oh,yeah. That.
好吧，如果这么重要 我就让给你吧
If it means that much,I'll let you have her.
谢了
Thanks.
让给我？
"Let me have her"?
你是说如果你不让 我就没有机会？
You mean if you didn't,I wouldn't have a shot?
我没有说得这么明显，不过…
I don't like to say it out loud...
没错
... but yeah!
别难过，我们各有优点 你比较有数学头脑
We all have our strengths. You're better with numbers and stuff.
数学？你说我数学好？
Math? You're giving me math?
好，这样吧，算了
All right,you know what? Forget about it.
你去追她，我们看谁能追到
You go for the girl. We'll see who gets her.
我要你左边防守 而亲爱的 你…
I want you to run a post-pattern to the left. And,sweetie
对，我知道，跑远一点
Yeah,I know. Go long.
我就只是跑来跑去而已
All I'm doing is running back and forth from the huddle.
你要不要干脆留在场外好了？
Well,you wanna just stay out there?
我能看一秒钟这个东西吗？
Can I see that for a second?
好，来吧
Okay,let's go.
我来防守钱德 挡下开球
-I got Chandler! -Hike!
一个密西西比、两个密西西比、三个密西西比
One Mississippi,two Mississippi,three Mississippi.
漏接
Fumble!
你是怎么搞的？ 这是我最喜欢的一件毛织杉
What's the matter with you? This is my favorite jersey.
那你现在有两件了
Well,now you have two.
嘿，我的数学还真不赖
Hey,I am good at math!
够了，我本来还想让给你
That's it. I was still gonna let you have her.
现在你想都不要想 等着看自己出丑吧
But now,prepare to feel bad about yourself.
我已经准备了一辈子了
I've been preparing for that my entire life!
我等着看你出丑
Or something about you that's mean!
快点，比赛了
Come on,guys. Let's go.
比数拉平，我们没时间了
Tie score. We're running out of time.
42、38，挡下开球
Forty-two,38,hike!
我接到了
I got it!
我的胸部骨折了
Broken boobs!
菲比，快跑 快跑，菲比，快跑
-Pheebs,run! -Run,Phoebe,run!
触地得分！
Touchdown! Touchdown!
铃声响了，不算
The buzzer buzzed. It doesn't count.
那是在传球之前 在传球之后
-After the snap. -Before the snap.
之后 之前
-After. -Before.
这很重要吗？ 对
-Does it really matter? -Yes!
但我触地得分了 这是我的第一次
But I made a touchdown. It was my first touchdown.
菲比，太好了 可是不算
Pheebs,that's great. Doesn't count.
当然算 骗子，骗子，不吃会死
-Does so count. -Cheater,cheater,compulsive eater.
我的天啊
Oh,my God!
很好，也许你还没长大 但我已经是大人了
That's fine. Maybe you haven't grown up,but I have.
踢死你
Dead leg!
好，很好… 你想靠作弊赢球，随便你
Okay,fine. You want to win by cheating,go ahead.
菲比，得分照算，你赢了
The touchdown does count. You win.
我不想再跟你吵 我要你输得无话可说
I won't do this again. I wanna beat you when you can't blame it...
不能怪罪鼻梁断掉、铃声 或是你可能白血球过多
...on the broken nose or the buzzer or the fact that you might have mono.
比赛算平手，现在是中场休息
Let's just call this tie score and it's halftime.
首先，我不跟作弊的人比赛
First,I don't play with cheaters.
第二，你知道 我以前有腺体肿大的毛病
Second of all,you know I had swollen glands!
你知道吗？我看你一定会参加
You know what? I think you'll play.
真的吗？为什么？
Oh,really? Why's that?
因为赢的人可以拿到这个
Because the winner gets this.
盖勒杯
The Geller Cup!
你们大家也看见一个 钉在小木板上的娃娃吗？
Is everybody else seeing a troll doll nailed to a two-by-four?
好，很好
Okay,good.
你是从哪里弄来的？
Where the hell did you get that?
你到医院去接鼻梁的时候…
When you went to the hospital for your nose...
我游到湖里找出来的
...I swam into the lake and fished it out.
奖杯是我的
That cup is mine!
才不是，你想要 就得凭本事来赢过去
No,it's not. You want it,you're gonna have to win it.
那我们不吃晚饭了？
So are we not having dinner at all?
嘿，你能帮忙设置一下时间吗，玛嘉
Hey, could you please set the timer, Margha?
好的，比菲
Okay, Beefy.
过来，该认真一点了，围过来
Come on,let's go. It's time to get serious. Huddle up.
乔伊，认真比赛
IKeep your head in the game.
这很难耶 他就在那个荷兰女孩旁边
It's hard,you know? His huddle's close to the Dutch girl.
如果我让钱德出局 你能够专心吗？
If I take Chandler out of the running,will you be able to focus?
你有什么办法？ 你只要让他接到球就好了
-What are you gonna do? -Just make sure he catches the ball.
其他就交给我吧
I'll do the rest.
来吧 懦夫  来
-Come on,you wuss! -Okay,come on.
看我的
I got it!
来，这里，来
Come on! This way! Come on!
小心
Look out!
被女生阻截 这种画面不多见吧
Tackled by a girl! Bet you don't see that every day.
你这是干嘛？
What's with the tackling?
干嘛？
What?
我碰他一下，他就倒下来了
I just touched him and he went over.
好，你想玩狠的 我们也可以很野蛮
Okay. You wanna play rough? We can play rough.
准备开打
Let's get ready to rumble!
加油 挡住她
-Go,go,go! -Get her! Get her!
我爱这个比赛！
I love this game!
你从哪里弄来的？
Where'd you get that?
我跑得很远
I went really long.
42比21
Forty-two to 21.
罗斯跟火鸡一样死翘翘了
Like the turkey,Ross is done!
你会赢并不奇怪，你先挑人 挑到的球员比较好
You got to pick first,so you got the better team.
你真可悲，为什么 你不肯承认我们赢球
Pathetic! Why can't you just accept that we're winning...
是因为我比你行？
... because I'm better than you?
好啊，好一声叹息
Oh,what a great argument. Exhaling!
好，我要让你心服口服
All right,I'll prove it to you.
我用乔伊跟你换瑞秋 还是照赢不误
I'll trade you Joey for Rachel and I'll still win the game.
哦，很好，这是我最后的自尊
Oh, that's great.There goes my last shred of self-esteem.
什么？男生对女生？
What? The guys against the girls?
这太荒谬了，因为我只要 三次触地得分，就追上你了
That's ridiculous because I'm only down by three touchdowns.
那就得分给我看啊
Then bring it on!
除非你怕会输给几个女生
Unless you're afraid you might lose to a bunch of girls.
很好，瑞秋，你跟莫妮卡 乔伊，你跟我一队
Fine. Rachel,you're with Monica. Joey,you're with me.
你竟然把我交换出去
I can't believe you're trading me.
你马上就要输了
You are going to lose.
你马上就要输了，并且…
And you are going to lose.And....
帮帮我，我从没这么说过
Help me out.l've never done this before.
很好，失败，失败
That's good. Lose.Lose!
我们也来尝尝看赢球的滋味
Let's see what it's like to be on a winning team for a change.
你会让我上场？
You're gonna let me play?
好了，那么
All right,then!
比赛结束了？我们要去吃饭？
The game is over? We eat now?
比赛还没结束 我们在交换球员
The game's not over. We're switching teams.
钱德觉得我对他造成威胁 还是跟他同一队比较好
Chandler finds me so intimidating that it's better if we're on the same team.
好，我们来打球吧，快
Okay,let's play. Let's go.
等一下
Hold on a second.
荷兰人是从哪里来的？
Where do Dutch people come from?
这个嘛 宾夕法尼亚州的荷兰人来自宾夕法尼亚
Well,the Pennsylvania Dutch come from Pennsylvania.
其他的荷兰人呢？
And the other Dutch people?
他们是荷兰附近来的吧？
They come from somewhere near the Netherlands,right?
勇气可嘉
Nice try.
梦幻岛（与荷兰谐音）是虚构出来的地方
The Netherlands is this make-believe place...
是彼得潘和小仙女的家（《小飞侠》）
...where Peter Pan and Tinker Bell live.
我的天
Oh,my.
别再讲“疯子的地理学”了 我们打球吧
Enough "geography for the insane." Let's play ball.
我不跟这家伙一起打球
I'm not playing with this guy.
我无所谓 我受够了
-Fine with me. -I've had enough of this.
干脆直截了当一点 海蒂，你喜欢哪一个？
Let's just cut to the chase. Heidi,which of my boys do you like?
你这是干嘛？
What are you doing?
我喜欢哪一个？
Which do I like?
对，你会挑哪一个约会 找乐子、带回你的“磨坊”？
Yeah,for dating,general merriment,taking back to your windmill?
如果一定要现在选…
Well,if I had to choose right now...
我也觉得不可思议…
...which,by the way,I find really weird...
不过我会说是钱德
... I would have to say Chandler.
等等，她显然没听懂你的问题
Wait a minute. She didn't understand the question.
你可以请虎克船长（《小飞侠》） 解释给她听啊
Why don't you have Captain Hook explain it to her?
对不起，这是我的真心话
I'm sorry. That is my truth.
听到没有？这是她的真心话 说什么“我把她让给你”！
You hear that? That is her truth,Mr. "I'll Let You Have Her"!
我赢了，你输了 我是决策者
I win! You suck! I rule all!
给我来个迷你波浪舞
Mini-wave in celebration of me!
我现在考虑要把我的答案 改成“谁都不选”
I am now thinking I would like to change my answer to "no one."
什么？
What?
我现在觉得你既肤浅…
I now find you shallow...
又呆瓜
...and a dork.
再见
Bye-bye.
干得好
Nice going.
你可以好几个月保存你做爱的精力了
You just saved yourself a couple months of sex.
这无所谓，因为她选的是我
It doesn't matter,because she picked me.
从现在起，我会跟女人约会
From now on,I get the dates...
而你周末的晚上只能 在家里看“简单烹饪”节目
...and you stay home on Saturday nights watching Ready,Set,Cook!
把这些话留着告诉心理医生 比赛快结束了
Save the breakthroughs for therapy. The clock is ticking.
我们时间不多 目前还落后给女生
We have no time and we are losing to girls.
我们不会输给女生
We're not gonna lose to girls.
现在比数是42比21
It's 42-21!
该死 我刚才就是领先这么多分
This sucks! I was just up by that much!
看，让我们这样想
Look, let me put it this way.
如果我们输了，她们会让我们记一辈子
lf we lose, they will never let us forget it.
更糟的是，她们会让跟你们约会的女人记一辈子
Okay, and worse than that, they'll never let the women you date forget it.
我们还要不要玩球？ 快点，你们这些娘娘腔
Are we playing football or what? Come on,you hairy-backed Marys!
我们必须要赢 我们要替全世界的女人而战
We have to do this. We're playing for women everywhere.
想想过去的每个烂约会
Think about every lousy date you ever had.
每个在亲热的时候 一只眼睛还在电视上的男人
Every guy who kept one eye on the TV while you were making out.
老天，你跟装假眼的 男人约会过？
Oh,my God. You dated someone with a glass eye too?
拜托你们，好吗？ 为了全体妇女，我们宰了他们
Come on,okay? This is for all womankind. Let's kill them!
对，宰了他们
Yeah! IKill them!
好啊，我也想宰了他们
All right,I want to kill them too.
可是他们是男生
But they're boys.
我们怎么打败三个男生？
You know,how are we gonna beat three boys?
只剩下一分半钟 我们还落后两分
A minute and a half left and we're down by two points.
还落后两分，姐妹们
Two points,ladies.
菲比，你再用后转身进攻法
Phoebe,you do a buttonhook again.
瑞秋，你跑远一点
Rachel,you go long.
不要再叫我跑远一点了 让我做点事，他们从不防守我
No,don't make me go long. Use me. They never cover me.
亲爱的，这是有原因的
Honey,there's a reason.
我不是跛脚，好吗？ 我可以发挥作用
I'm not lame,okay? I can do something.
你让我传球嘛 这也是我的比赛
Would you let me throw? This is my game too.
让她传球
Let her throw the ball.
迅速到他们后面，我传球给你 你传球到前场给菲比
Sweep behind,I'll pitch it. You throw it downfield to Phoebe.
谢谢
Thank you.
比赛开始 比赛开始
-Break! -Break!
好，来吧
All right,here we go.
31、71，挡下开球
Thirty-two,71,hike!
一个密西西比、两个密西西比、三个密西西比
One Mississippi,two Mississippi,three Mississippi!
加油…
Go,go,go!
接球
Catch it!
对不起，你还好吧？ 不，我不好
-I'm so sorry. Are you okay? -No,I'm not okay!
他们冲着我来 我不知道该怎么办
They were coming at me and I didn't know what to do.
比赛还剩下30秒钟
Thirty seconds left on the timer.
你们是失败者
You are the loser!
我们就可以 把那个呆瓜侏儒带回家了
So we get to take that stupid troll thing home.
快过来，我们没时间了
Come on! Hurry! We're running out of time.
临场会议
Huddle up!
这是最后一次临场会议了
This is our last huddle!
好，菲比，摆脱防守，瑞秋
All right,Phoebe,get open. Rachel...
跑远一点
...go long.
好
Okay.
结束
Break!
我成功了，触地得分，成功了
I did it! Touchdown! We did it!
你们知道吗？很奇怪 结束区是在那个柱子那里
You know? Funny thing,actually. The end zone starts at that pole.
所以你还差了五尺，所以…
So you're five feet short. So...
我们赢了
...we win!
太好了
Yes,yes,yes!
等等，请你们解释一下
Wait,explain something,though.
如果没有人抱住瑞秋 那比赛就还没结束吧？
If nobody tagged Rachel,then isn't the play still going?
让开… 想都别想，放手
-Let me in,let me in! -No way! Let go!
放手？我是个小女人
Let go?! I'm a tiny little woman!
拜托，今天是感恩节
Come on,it's Thanksgiving!
输赢并不重要
It's not important who wins or loses.
重要的是荷兰女孩选了我
The important thing is the Dutch girl picked me!
是我，不是你，荷兰爱钱德 谢谢，阿姆斯特丹，晚安
Me,not you! Holland loves Chandler! Thank you,Amsterdam! Good night!
我们应该多抽空玩足球
We should play football more often.
也许我们可以参加哪个联盟
Maybe there's a league we could join.
不是有个 “国家足球联盟”吗？
Isn't there a "national football league"?
没错，星期天 和星期一晚上比赛
Yes,there is. They play on Sundays and Monday nights.
太可惜了 我星期一晚上要上班
Oh,shoot! I work Monday nights.
这菜真好吃 要给他们带一些过去吗？
This stuffing is amazing. Do you think we should bring them some?
他们饿了自然会进来
When they're hungry,they'll come in.
放手 不，你放手
-Let go! -No,you let go!
为什么每次都只剩 我们两个人抱着球不放？
How come it's always us left holding the ball?
不知道，我想是因为 其他人不太在乎吧
I don't know. I guess the other people just don't care enough.
开始下雪了
Hey,it's starting to snow.
把球给我，放手 放手，快放手
-Give it to me! Let go! -Let it go! Come on,let go!
今晚我的脚趾头一度没有感觉了
There was a time tonight that l started losing the feeling in my toes.
-我知道 -那时我才发现…
-l know.-That's when l realized...
在比赛时还有比打你更重要的事
...there's more important things than beating you at football.
比如脚
Things like feet.
是的，我知道，这事让我们遭受太多痛苦了
Yeah, l know. This thing has caused us too much pain and suffering.
-是的 -到时间了
-Yeah.-lt's time.
我们就当平局好了
We'll just call it a tie.
-是平局 -好
-lt's a tie.-All right.
这里
Here.
好
Okay.
-晚安 -晚安
-Good night.-Good night.
菲比，你拿到了吗
Pheebs, did you get it?
-是的 -太棒了
-Yeah, l got it.-Oh, great.
带它上来，我房间里有胜利者的香槟
Bring it up. There's champagne in my apartment for the winners.
-罗斯，你在下面干什么？-没什么
-Ross! What are you doing down here?-Nothing.